Guide to the Alexander Jackson Davis Architectural Drawing Collection 1827-1884 PR 16
New-York Historical Society
- Wildmont - First Lodge "14 Beams over Parlor 2d sotry floor" ink BM, 93254 (Item 253g)
  "A. J. Davis's summer lodge, later expanded 1878. In wrapper: "Wildmont - First Lodge not wanted for new lodge." draft of will on verso
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Basement No. 1. Old House" ink, graphite, 93253 (Item 253h)
  "A. J. Davis's summer lodge, later expanded 1878. In wrapper: "Wildmont - First Lodge not wanted for new lodge." WM: JWhatman 1868
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93252 (Item 253q verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93251 (Item 253i verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "And he shall direct thy paths in all thy ways acknowledge him" graphite BR-UR, 93250 (Item 253u verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Cove molding in west chamber ceiling" graphite UL, 93249 (Item 253j verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Section Library and plan. North End" ink, graphite BL-BR, 93248 (Item 253k recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93247 (Item 253l)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93246 (Item 253m)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93245 (Item 253n recto)
  A. J. Davis's summer lodge, later expanded 1878. In wrapper: "Wildmont - First Lodge not wanted for new lodge." 11 x 14" paper folded 1/2.
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Flora's Dict." ink UM, 93244 (Item 253o recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93243 (Item 253o verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Front door" graphite BM, 93242 (Item 253p)
- Wildmont - First Lodge [unidentifiable subject matter], 93241 (Item 253q recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Lodge Study north end" graphite UL-UR, 93240 (Item 253r)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93239 (Item 253s)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93238 (Item 253t recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "North End" graphite UL, 93237 (Item 253t verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Section North End Wildmont lodge looking east" ink, graphite UM, 93236 (Item 253t recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Things yet to do at lodge", 93235 (Item 253c recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge "Section of Library looking south. Looking North" ink, graphite CM, CM, 93234 (Item 253j recto)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, 93233 (Item 253n verso)
- Wildmont - First Lodge, Wadell Window/ Wildmont Window "Wadell Bay wnidow sahs 22 by 112 glass 16 x 26 Built into bay at Wildmont." ink, graphite UR, 93232 (Item 253b)
- Winslow Residence "Study for Winslow." ink LL, 93231 (Item 156a recto)
  unidentified project; see also verso and #156b
- Winslow Residence "Study for Winslow." ink and graphite LR, 93230 (Item 156a verso)
  unidentified project; see also recto and #156b
- Winslow Residence "CORNER LOT." watercolor LR, 93229 (Item 156a verso)
  collage; unidentified project; see also #156a recto-verso
- View Through a Monumental Greek Portico, 93228 (Item 575)
- "12. Window over Drawing room bay. Window over front porch.", 93227 (Item 251a)
- unidentified project, 93226 (Item 276c)
- unidentified project, 93225 (Item 276)
- unidentified project, 93223 (Item 250)
  similar to early 300 series drawings, wm: "JWhatman 1868"
- unidentified project, 93222 (Item 001c)
- unidentified project, 93221 (Item 204)
- unidentified project, 93220 (Item [605])
- unidentified project, 93219 (Item 452)